{
    "id": "69180328ae5e4ae18d493347862bd141",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You ……………. not spit on the road. (Prohibition)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "will",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………. not steal. (Prohibition)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "must"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. behave herself. (Necessity)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. obey the rules. (Obligation)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "shall",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If you have finished your job, you ………………. go. (Permission)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "will",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. speak four languages. (Ability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………. read when she was just three years old. (Past ability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………….. stand on his head. (Ability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "will",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother is eighty. She ……………. still read without glasses. (Ability)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I borrow your camera? (Permission)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "May",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I’m starving.’ ‘I …………….. get you something to eat.’ (Willingness)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}